jukinmedia.com 2018-06-16

# Privacy Policy | Jukin Media

The privacy policy set forth below are applicable to the web site located at www.JukinMedia.com, its operational host Jukin Technologies, Inc., and each of their respective affiliates, parents, subsidiaries, licensees, and assigns (collectively hereinafter referred to, alternatively, as “JukinMedia,” the “Site,” “we,” “us,” “our” or similar identifying pronouns). JukinMedia strives to provide the best service possible to its users. When you share information with us about yourself (including without limitation by becoming a member or simply by using the Site), we collect this information and may use it in different ways with the goal of developing, improving, protecting and providing even better services.

By using the Site you are agreeing to our Terms of Service and Privacy Policy. As part of our service we collect certain information in order to learn from our visitors and improve our services. Information may be provided directly by you or through your usage of services and the Site, including third party sites and advertising linked or accessed from our Site. Such information may be gathered in a number of ways and from many sources, including without limitation, from a membership account, sign-in, IP address, service usage and views to specific content, visits to linked third party sites and/or advertising, device-specific information (e.g. operating system, mobile network, related device identifiers, system activity, settings and the like), browser web storage and similar application data caches, cookies and other similar identifiers.

In order to provide a premiere level of service, JukinMedia works with various third party vendors, partners, advertisers and other service providers in different industries and types of business. Except as otherwise prohibited by Internet privacy legislation, JukinMedia reserves the right to share information it collects from the Site to its trusted partners. JukinMedia may also share information if we have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary (i) to enforce the Terms of Service; (ii) to investigate, prevent or take action in connection with potential violations of the Terms of Service or any potentially fraudulent, threatening or illegal activities; (iii) to investigate, prevent or take action in connection with potential technical issues; (iv) to respond to claims that any such information violates the rights of others; (v) to protect the rights, property or personal safety of JukinMedia, Jukin Technologies, its affiliates, parent, subsidiaries, suppliers and their respective directors, officers, employees and agents and/or users of or visitors to the Site, and the public; (vi) to respond to court orders, subpoenas or otherwise exercise JukinMedia’s legal rights and/or defend against legal claims; and (vii) as otherwise required by any applicable law, regulation, or enforceable judicial, administrative or governmental request.

JukinMedia is not responsible or liable for information it obtains about its users through the Site or which it shares pursuant to the terms of this Privacy Policy and its Terms of Service. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we do regularly review our compliance with our Privacy Policy and aim to protect our Site and our users from unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, copying, disclosure or destruction of information we hold. Some of the measures we may take include the periodic review of our information collection, storage and processing practices (including physical security measures) to guard against unauthorized access to systems and restricting access to personal information to those employees, contractors, partners and agents who need to know that information in order to process it for us, and who are subject to contractual confidentiality obligations and may be disciplined or terminated if they fail to meet these obligations. While we reserve the right to take appropriate confidentiality and security measures, you should not have any expectation of privacy when using the Site or the Internet generally. Internet users may best protect their privacy through controlled disclosure of personal information. In order to keep their information private, users need to be careful what they submit, provide, disclose, review and look at online, including in connection with the Site. Should you wish to enhance your privacy, you may wish to explore higher security settings on your computer. You may also decide to set your browser to block cookies; however, please understand that many of our services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. If you are a parent, you may elect to use parental control settings on your device to prevent, limit or control access to the site.

Please click [HERE](https://www.jukinmedia.com/terms-eu) for additional privacy policies that may apply to you.

By using the Site you are agreeing to our Terms of Service and to the terms of our Privacy Policy as set forth herein. We reserve the right to make changes to our Terms of Service and our Privacy Policy at any time. It is your responsibility to periodically review the Terms of Service and Privacy Policy and be aware of our current terms, JukinMedia’s rights and your responsibilities and duties in connection with protecting any information you wish to keep private or confidential. Unless otherwise specified, any changes shall be effective when they are posted, and your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes will mean that you accept and agree to the changes.

##### Effective May 25, 2018
